Adam Hoff

(571) 439-9011 | adamhoff79@gmail.com | 16667 Goldencrest Circle, Purcellville VA 20132

Profile

WEB DEVELOPER

A 20 year old junior full-stack web developer with a passion for all things technology, I am able to work calmly and productively and finish the task at hand while under high stress and pressure. I am a quick learner, grasping new skills and ideas without hesitation and I am able to implement these skills throughout my work. My optimism and curiosity for web development will only keep growing as I continue to use innovating technologies to create stunning front-end designs and formulate clever solutions to back-end obstacles.

Experience

LIFEGUARD, FRANKLIN PARK POOL

MAY 2012-SEP 2016

Red Cross CPR and First Aid trained and certified. Helped teach new employees how to handle emergency situations at our facility; ensured compliance with established rules and guidelines by both employees and patrons; helped maintain constant surveillance of patrons within the facility; assisted with pool maintenance. Through the performance of numerous rescues while on duty, I learned how to perform well under stress and pressure. When needed, I acted immediately and appropriately to secure safety of patron sin the event of an emergency, providing emergency care and treatment as required until the arrival of emergency medical services

LIFEGUARD, STONELEIGH GOLF & COUNTRY CLUB

MAY 2014-AUG 2015

Red Cross CPR and First Aid trained and certified. helped maintain constant surveillance of patrons within the facility; ensured compliance with established rules and guidelines by patrons; assisted with pool maintenance.

Education

University of Mary Washington, Fredericksburg VA

General Assembly; Web Development Immersive, Washington D.C.

Mar 2017-June 2017

Areas of Expertise

	Front-end development		Agile programming	ı	Object oriented programming
	Front-end design		Git workflows	1	Team collaborating
Technical Skills					
	HTML	CSS	JavaScript		jQuery
	Bootstrap	Ruby on Rails	AngularJS		PostgressQL
Projects					

http://adamhoff.github.io/portfolio

Front-end portfolio containing my projects and other information about myself.